Robert Ginter

I have experience with Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator/Experience Design, Sketch and the prototyping platform InVision. I use those skills to create wireframes, prototypes, userflows and countless other design elements. I also have some skill in web development, using HTML, CSS and Javascript.

Technical abilities

- Design software: Adobe Photoshop/Illustrator/Experience Design, InVision, Sketch, Balsamiq, Axure
- Web development: HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Google Analytics
- General computer skills: Microsoft Word/Excel/Powerpoint, Outlook, Github, Dropbox

Language skills

- Estonian C2
- English C2
- German A2

Design portfolio

www.robertginter.com

Experience

Freelance graphic designer - 2012 - 2016

- Creating raster graphics, web design and photo manipulation using Adobe Photoshop.
- Creating website wireframes using Balsamiq or Adobe Experience Design.
- Creating web design prototypes using Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Sketch and Invision.

Alternative service - 21.11.2016 - 08.11.2017

- Managing and updating a company website.
- Teaching people basic computer skills.

UX Designer at Velvet Design Agency – 23.01.2018 – present

- Creating interactive website prototypes using Sketch and InVision.
- Planning, designging and conducting user testing interviews.
- Conducting user experience desk research
- Designing and presenting my findings.

Education

Gustav Adolfi Gümnaasium - 2002 - 2011

Primary and middle school

Liivalaia Gümnaasium - 2011 - 2014

High school

Tallinna University - 2014 - 2016

University